Nori, just one more time, okay?
Mom, where are you going?
I'll just be gone for a bit.
Thanks, Nick.
I'll see you soon.
Excuse me.
I'm Detective Murphy.
Who's my first responder?
Over there.
That's me.
Homeless guy called it in.
It's, uh... I've never seen
anything like that before.
When did you get here?
A few minutes before midnight.
Has anyone else been inside?
Ju... just me and my partner
here, uh, one of the EMTs,
and, uh, Lieutenant...
Welcome back, Detective.
Picked a hell of a night
to come back to work.
Well, I hope you're
not here to babysit me.
I'm not.
I was halfway home
when I got the call.
I was getting a lot of
chatter about this one.
Oh, yeah, why's that?
You should probably pop
your head in and take a look.
Ah, good to see you.
You, too.
You ready for this?
It's all you.
Let me know if
you need anything.
What is this?
She's completely charred, and
there's no evidence of a fire.
I know, exactly.
The homeless guy, did he
call in a body or a fire?
Nothing about a
fire, just the body.
"Kyoko Oshiro," what
happened to you?
Mrs. Oshiro?
Hi.
I'm Detective Stella Murphy.
Can I come in for a minute?
Okay, so she left the apartment
last night at around 9:45?
And did she tell you
where she was going?
Who killed her?
That's what I'm going
to find out, Mrs. Oshiro.
Do you know anyone
who would want
to hurt Kyoko, any friends,
family, co-workers?
Ma'am, I know that
this is very difficult,
but would you be willing to come
down and identify Kyoko's body?
I cannot.
I understand.
Before I go, would you mind
if I took a look around?
Thank you.
Yeah, hold on one sec.
Yeah?
Can you send IT over?
I need to change my password.
For what?
Because it's still Mara.
Yeah, I'll send someone over.
So we don't have any
dental records to match to.
Logic obviously points
to this being Ms. Oshiro.
Yeah, I figured as much.
Family is not going
to come identify.
I don't blame them.
This body, I ran
carbon-14 dating
on her a couple of
times, even recalibrated
the machine to make sure
something wasn't wrong.
Each reading put this body
at more than 1,000 years old.
She wasn't burnt.
She's petrified.
I want to see Mom.
You cannot.
Why not?
We will hear from the police
when they find something.
Don't you want to see her?
We will not speak
about this anymore.
Yeah?
I need an APB sent out.
On who?
The homeless man who called
in the body, Rudolfo Sanchez,
he has a prior for
arson a few years back.
Call you back?
Thanks.
You got anything else?
Is this the level of supervision
I can expect from now on?
I was wondering.
Do you have any idea why a
woman who was born 42 years ago
has been dead for 1,000 years?
Anyway, that's how the,
uh, chain of command works.
Right.
Are you gonna have
a problem with that?
No.
I left.
You stayed, got a promotion.
I'm proud of you.
Stella, Stella.
Sorry.
I tried your first.
She wouldn't stop
asking for you.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Nori, is everything okay?
I was wondering if
I could see my mom.
Um.
I'd really like to see her.
Yeah, I understand.
Um, honey, I don't know if
that's a good idea right now.
You... you don't want
to see her like this.
I need to.
How old are you, again?
I'm 18.
Is your grandma here, Nori?
No.
Let's go.
This is never easy.
Okay.
No.
So this is her.
Can I come in?
Not right now.
No, ma'am, was there
something you didn't tell me?
Your daughter's body was
petrified, and the tests we ran
came back saying she'd been
dead nearly 1,000 years.
I don't mean to overstep here.
But your granddaughter,
something happened to Nori
when she saw her mother's body.
Now considering the two
strangest things I have ever
seen in my life happened
with your family,
I'm thinking you could
tell me something.
You could not
possibly understand.
What happened?
My Kaisho.
And the detective saw.
I didn't mean to.
Nori, these people cannot know.
There's no point in it.
What?
You must not be seen.
You cannot...
How you doing?
It's a weird one, more questions
than answers at this point.
No, I mean, how are you?
Oh, I'm fine.
Just checking.
I can still do that, right?
Yeah, I wouldn't be here
if I wasn't all right.
Have a good night.
Jake.
Jake!
Stella, what are you doing?
I got to do my laundry.
Excuse me.
You been drinking?
I don't like seeing
you like this.
Jake, can you just please
stop it with all this, like,
supervisor...
Are you kidding me right now?
My wife comes to our
house that she hasn't
been to in months, drunk.
You think I don't have
a right to be concerned?
Fine.
I'm not asking you to be fine.
I'm asking you to be careful.
Okay.
What the fuck is that?
Ow.
I don't know when you got into
this rogue I can, like, suffer
through this on my
own bullshit, but it
doesn't have to be that way.
You're not the only one in pain.
Oh, that's funny, because
it didn't really seem
like it bothered you that much.
I'll let myself out.
Yeah, why don't you
take a fucking cab?
I don't want tea.
Why didn't you or
Mom ever explain
what was going to happen to me?
A Kaisho is something you
must discover for yourself.
It is our sacred
gift to bring back
what is beautiful in the world.
But you must not be seen until
you can learn to control it.
Noriko, your mother did not want
you to grow up living in fear.
So instead, we chose to
stay hidden from the world?
I was so lost yesterday.
You should not have gone.
I needed to see her.
I just want things to be normal.
Do not complain
about what is normal.
You are not normal.
Your Kaisho is more important
than your happiness.
It is your responsibility.
Murphy.
I don't think you're
ready to be back.
Why, because of last night?
I'm sorry.
What time is it?
Am I late for work, Jake?
I don't understand.
What's the problem?
Oh, I don't know,
drunk driving, maybe.
I'm going to recommend
you go back out on leave.
Oh, okay, don't go
on a power trip.
You need more time.
No, I don't need more time.
What I need is to stay busy.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Last night was stupid,
and it was reckless.
It won't happen again.
But if you're really
worried about me,
you'll let me do my job.
I promise it's what's
best for me right now.
I can bring this case home.
You just need to let me.
If for a second I don't
think you can handle it,
I'm pulling you back off.
All right.
Evening, what can I get you?
Hi.
I'm looking for Davis.
Is he here?
I'll get him.
Ordering anything?
Yeah, a cup of
coffee would be great.
Thank you.
It's clean, just
the humidity makes
everything a little sticky.
I didn't want you to
think things were dirty.
What can I do for you, miss?
I'm Detective Stella Murphy.
I just have some questions
about Kyoko Oshiro.
Uh.
Do you want to
talk somewhere else?
She asked me to do it.
Excuse me?
Look.
I don't want to make
this into some big deal.
But, uh, I don't make
a lot of money here.
I'm barely managing
to keep the lights on.
With all that's
going on out there,
I don't know how
you guys can come
down on me for paying somebody
a few dollars under the table.
Okay.
So what is it, a fine?
Did she report this?
She hasn't even been here
for the last two shifts.
Mr. Davis, I work homicide.
Kyoko was found
dead four days ago.
Can I help you?
Mom?
No, Kyoko had a
child and responsibility.
She was taking
care of her mother.
There's no world in which
she would do this to herself.
Because it's not.
Jake, she never
even went to school.
Nobody knows anything about her.
I don't know, but it
seems like Kyoko was
just keeping her hidden inside.
Or maybe she was... she was
trying to keep something out.
I don't know.
Hello.
Wait.
What?
What is this?
I think this is
who killed my mom.
It happened in my mom's room.
It was something in this book.
I thought that maybe I could do
it again to see who killed her.
Have you ever done anything
like that before or seen it?
No.
But I've grown up
learning about my family,
that we're connected
to something very old.
There used to be more like us,
but people are afraid of what
they don't understand.
I used to feel so
safe around her.
Now it's as if I'm in
this giant sea and...
It just seems endless?
Yes.
I know that man.
Mr. Davis has always
been very nice to us.
Anytime I was sick, he would
bring over soup to our home.
She said she really
liked working here.
Do you like your job?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, it's not easy,
but, yeah, I like it.
Might not be the best way
to look at it, but sometimes
when you see how bad
it can be for people
it forces you to evolve
in more ways than one.
That's good, right?
Yeah.
Whether or not you're
growing closer or farther
from the things in your
life, it's just important
that you're growing, right?
Have a good night, okay?
You, too.
Bye.
Shh, shh.
Yeah, this is Detective
Stella Murphy.
I need all available units.
She have someplace to go?
Uh, yeah, we're working
on that right now.
Well, I think it's safe to say
the killer knows the family.
What?
The entire
apartment was trashed,
but Nori's room was untouched.
Hey, let's get you
out of here, okay?
I'll call you later.
Can I stay with you tonight?
Come on in.
So I can get you some
sheets for the couch.
Okay, so here are
some, uh, blankets.
Is a t-shirt okay?
Um, you can turn on
the TV if you want.
I don't have cable, but...
Also I usually keep some
music on while I sleep.
Is that okay?
Um.
Do you want one?
Does it hurt?
Yeah, a little.
I used to have this
townhouse with my ex.
Ex?
Ex-husband,
I used to be married.
Oh.
Yeah, we had this place.
It wasn't anything fancy,
but it was our dream home.
Anyway, one night, I was lying
in bed, and all of a sudden I
heard this dripping sound.
I was just lying
there, listening to it,
waiting for it to go away
or waiting until I stopped
caring about it or something.
But neither happened,
so I got up.
And I... I went to
go look for it,
just searching around
for this dripping sound.
And all the faucets
were turned off,
and the windows were closed.
I'm just looking for
this little, like, drip,
drip, drip, drip, drip, drip.
So finally, I... I went
out into the hallway.
And I could hear that it was
coming from inside the wall.
There was really nothing I
could do, short of putting
a hammer through the wall.
So I just went back to bed.
And I tried to go to
sleep, but I couldn't.
And then it happened again the
next night, and the next night,
and the next night.
So I got one of those
little, uh, music players.
And I, um, I would
play my favorite jazz
albums so I could sleep.
The first night, I could
still kind of hear the drip,
but then it just
kind of went away.
You know, sometimes noise is so
loud that you just have to make
your own to cover it up.
The radiators in our house
used to make a loud banging.
Yeah?
We got them fixed.
I brought you some coffee.
I'm not supposed to.
Okay.
I'll just leave it
here if you want it.
So we have somewhere we
need to be this morning.
Why don't you hop in the shower?
I left a towel and
some clothes for you.
Okay.
Okay, just sign right there.
I'll make sure your grandma
is right next to her, okay?
Thank you.
Hey.
Hey!
It's a sports bike, no plates.
Rider is in all black gear.
I think male, but
don't hold me to that.
Okay, yeah, let me know.
What did they say?
Well, it's not much,
but it's out to dispatch.
It's not much to go
on, but you never know.
He's coming for me.
Hey, I'm not going to
let anything happen to you.
Yeah.
Being a detective just
seems like asking a lot
of people a lot of questions.
You're not wrong about
that, but you also need
to know how to read people.
It's not about their answers.
It's about how they answer.
Mr. Davis.
Ladies, any news?
Has a man in a motorcycle outfit
ever come in here to
talk to my mother?
Yeah.
Yeah, last week, she had
an argument with some guy.
He came in.
He was decked out
from head to toe.
What?
What were they arguing about?
I don't speak Japanese.
Well, what?
I... I thought he was a
customer, someone she knew.
I don't know.
I asked you.
And I just remembered it.
Do those work?
Do you recognize him?
No, just from today.
Are you sure?
Murph, my office, now.
I'll be back.
What the hell is she doing here?
Jake, she's an active
part of my investigation.
Okay, a civilian,
nonetheless a kid,
cannot be in the pen, pretending
to play junior detective.
I'm getting an idea on
some security footage.
Her entire family is dead.
We buried her mom this morning.
And in the process, we
found a possible suspect.
An arsonist.
This is not arson.
We can agree something crazy
is going on here, right?
We have run out of
words to describe
the state of these
bodies, let alone
how the killings
actually went down.
And that little girl
is at the center of it.
I know what this sounds
like, but she is special.
What do you expect
me to do with that?
I expect you to believe me.
All right, well, special
isn't going to cut it.
Especially since the
second body showed up,
we're getting a lot of
pressure from upstairs.
Oh, well, I'm sorry
you're having a tough time.
If you want to be helpful
to me, call immigration.
Check on the Oshiro family.
Murphy.
Hmm?
Stay close.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm okay.
All right.
Do you mind if I lay
down for a little while?
You're in the guest
bedroom upstairs.
Make yourself at home.
It's okay.
Hey.
You doing all right?
Come on.
You should have someone
go back to the apartment.
Um, maybe he left
something behind.
Maybe just do, like, a...
Yeah, I already...
I called already.
Okay.
It's good.
How long has she been
staying with you?
Two nights, ever
since her grandmother...
Stella...
I know.
It's not a good look.
Hey.
It's okay.
You're all right.
It's just been so weird,
having a kid around.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't anybody's fault.
She rolled onto her
stomach in the middle
of the night, which is something
she had never done before.
And when she was face down, her
neck wasn't strong enough yet
to turn to the side.
So she... she suffocated
in her sleep.
Nobody tells you how afraid you
become when you have a baby.
I used to wake up at the
slightest sound coming
from the monitor,
just so paranoid
that every movement or cough
or moan was something bad.
She was so quiet that night.
I'm sorry for going in there.
It's okay.
So I'll just, um, I'll just
set up in the living room.
Do you need anything?
Yeah, do you still have that
speaker from the holiday party?
Oh, I forgot to tell
you, I fixed the drip.
It's gone.
It's in the junk drawer.
Yeah.
All right, go ahead.
Right.
Immigration just called.
I got some information
on the Oshiros.
Yeah?
Oshiro Kyoko and Umaris
Yako immigrated in 1998.
Six months later,
they had Noriko.
Get this.
Supposedly, there's a son
in the family, Jin Oshiro,
wasn't on any of the
immigration records.
He was busted for assault
in '08, nothing since.
You think Nori knows about him?
Nori?
Oh, my God.
Hi.
I'm Jin.
You're Nori, right?
Did you kill them?
No.
It's more complicated than that.
But, yeah, I did.
Hey, did they ever mention me?
You killed my mother!
Nori!
No.
No, it's not like that, Nori.
They were not good people, okay?
They lied to you.
My mother would never lie.
I really wish that were true.
Nori, listen.
I'm your brother.
What?
I am your brother.
Wait.
For the rest of our
family, the Kaisho was
always beautiful, like yours.
But to Mother,
mine was wretched.
She'd never do that.
Trauma started the Kaisho.
The trauma is what
Mother gave to me.
When I was a boy,
Mother would take me
into the city on a train,
and I loved watching
the sunset through the window.
It was always beautiful.
But one day, a man
came into the train
and sat down very
close to Mother.
He was a bad man.
He was a bad guy.
He kept staring at her.
We got off the train.
He followed us in the dark.
And he showed up, and
he grabbed Mother.
I pulled his arm,
and it turned to ash.
But after that, Obaachan
looked at me as cursed.
She wouldn't speak to me.
I just wanted to
protect my mother.
But Mother, she thought
she could change me.
She pushed me hard,
pushed me to pain,
and pushed me to hating her.
And I even hated myself 'cause
I thought that was my fault.
Mother finally realized
my Kaisho wouldn't change.
It couldn't become
beautiful like yours.
So one day, Mother
took me to a park.
It was a cold day.
It was sunny.
Then she told me to wait.
I waited.
I waited for her to come back,
not knowing that my family had
gone to America.
She didn't need me anymore.
She had you.
When I felt the pain of
being abandoned for good,
my Kaisho grew stronger.
After years of honing this
power, I told myself, one day,
I'd find them and show
them what they left behind.
Nori.
Nori!
Let go of me!
Listen.
Listen!
All right?
Please.
It's okay.
I don't want to hurt you, Nori.
I want to help you.
And I can show you what you're
really able to do, all right?
It's okay.
See?
Take my hand.
It's okay.
See?
You feel it, huh?
Let me teach you.
Huh?
I can teach you.
It's all right.
It's okay.
All right, come on.
Come on.
It's okay.
Come with me.
Hey, come on.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hey.
Just grab what you need.
Murphy?
Nori.
Oh, my God, honey, are you okay?
What happened?
I don't know where to begin.
You made the right decision.
Let's do this.
He wasn't going to hurt me.
Yeah, sure.
Let's go.
Stay here.
I figure we play it
safe with this guy.
Good luck.
Mr. Oshiro, I'm
Detective Murphy.
Yeah, we met.
Not officially.
Can I ask you some questions?
Yeah, go ahead.
On September 1, you visited
Kyoko Oshiro at the diner
she works at, right?
Mm-hmm, yeah, I did.
Do you remember what
happened that night?
Oh, nothing special.
I just wanted to see my mother.
September 8, do you remember
where you were that night?
In the abandoned
warehouse on Spring Street,
where I killed my mother.
And a few days later, I killed
my grandmother in her home.
Why would you kill your
mother and your grandmother?
Family issues.
Did you love them?
I loved them.
I loved them, and I
wanted to be loved.
What did you do to them?
Did you burn them?
Not really.
Would you care to elaborate?
I could, but I bet you
would not understand.
Why don't you try me?
Okay, it's a shame
she died so young.
Do you want to see her?
I can show you, right
here, right now.
Huh?
Would you please
excuse me for a minute?
What the hell was that?
We got him.
He admitted to
both of the murders.
But I already told
you he killed them.
Yeah, well, uh, he admitted
it, so now we can arrest him.
He's done.
What happens to him?
Well, he gets
booked and processed.
Assuming he maintains
this admission of guilt,
he'll go to prison.
And then from there,
we'll know when and how
long he's locked up for.
Nori, what's going on?
Move, move.
Sergeant, move
over here with me.
Get over here now.
Watch the back door.
Go.
Get out of here.
Authorities are still gathering
information on the explosion
at the metropolitan police
station.
Lieutenant Tenwick,
we're ready in 20.
Let me talk to him first.
I can help.
No, Nori, he's too dangerous.
That's not going to happen.
That's my brother.
This is my fault.
I need to fix it.
Jake, I'll ping you
when we're ready, okay?
Murphy.
Give me a second.
It's okay.
Jake, I know this isn't what you
want to hear, but she's right.
Are you serious?
We're not going to pull her in the
middle of this. It's our job.
We don't even know what
we're dealing with here.
We have to do everything
we can to stop this guy,
and whatever Jin's got,
Nori's got it, too.
Can't, sorry.
Nori?
Nori!
Jin.
Are you alone?
Yes, but not for long.
Jin, they're coming for you.
I trusted you.
Do you hear me?
You don't deserve
what happened to you,
but that doesn't give you
the right to kill anyone.
Nori, listen.
I was rescuing you, okay?
It was all for you.
You murdered them.
Don't say that.
What about those
police, those paramedics?
Don't say that!
Jin, you have to
turn yourself in.
I know Mom and Obaachan
were not good to you.
What they did was
wrong, and I'm sorry.
You're just as
despicable as Mother.
Nori.
Nori!
Nori, stop!
Jake?
Jake, honey?
Oh, God, Jake.
Jake, you're okay, honey.
Oh, God.
You're okay.
You don't have to do this.
I'll go with you.
It's too late.
It will be nice to
have family again.
Are you sure you don't
want me to ride with you?
It's okay.
I need to figure
these things out.
Hey, so, um, I want
you to take this.
It's not that much, but
I think it'll help you.
Thank you.
Hey.
You will always have
a home here, okay?
Okay.
I'll be back.